<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Derek Borders</title>
    <link>https://derekborders.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Derek Borders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://derekborders.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from Grading Graduate Work as an Undergrad: 01</title>
      <link>https://derekborders.netlify.app/2022/02/10/grading-lessons-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://derekborders.netlify.app/2022/02/10/grading-lessons-01/</guid>
      <description>IntroThrough a short series of bureaucratic happenstances, I find myself grading for a graduate-level machine learning course as an undergraduate. I excelled in my undergraduate machine learning course and the curriculum is essentially the same. Nonetheless, I expect some interesting tidbits may be gleaned from the experience.
Part 1Technical StuffIn my first grading experience for the course, I have already learned or re-learned a few interesting things of a technical nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iris: The Hello World of Data Science</title>
      <link>https://derekborders.netlify.app/2022/02/07/iris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://derekborders.netlify.app/2022/02/07/iris/</guid>
      <description>IrisThe famous Iris data set is the ‘Hello World’ of data science.
It’s small enough to be easy to understand at a glance, but large enough to have some interesting and demonstrative properties. It’s great for exploring predictive and classification models, for regression and clustering and for unsupervised and supervised machine learning techniques.
Iris is just fun and colorful in a way that appeals to the kid in all of us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://derekborders.netlify.app/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://derekborders.netlify.app/cv/</guid>
      <description>Curriculum Vitae Derek Borders Education Chico State NWCU Law Shasta College Work Experience Student Assistant 20 Years in Service Industry Licenses &amp;amp; Certifications Licensed Attorney  2016-Present Currently Inactive  Projects laminar Point of Sale Miscellaneous National Cyber League Games (Spring 2021)  Individual Games  Done real good   Team Games  Done purty good too    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://derekborders.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://derekborders.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>Portfolio Project A Project B Project C </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
